AFSHIN ZALI

PROFIL

My work experience are breadth due to my interests, therefore the fluctuate lines of businesses. Most of the work has been writing. I'd worked in restaurants and with people. Documentation for higher authority has made me be meticulous about writing. That is why i chose to study copywriting in Forsbergs School in Stockholm.

EXPERIENCES

COLUMNIST, GÖTEBORGS-POSTEN - 2017 - NOW

Columnist for Sweden second largest newspaper. I write about music film and pop culture. Anecdotes linked with culture.

CONTACT PERSON, SDN MAJORNA/LINNÉ (SDN SÖDERMALM) – 2008-NOW In Sweden, a person who has a social illness such as Autism and Asperger Syndrome are entitled to get support from the county, usual a contact person. Breaking isolation that is often common with the social illnesses. Help them with their social life. Taking

them out for "FIKA" (coffee and biscuits). I work with 3 kids with different levels of autism.

TREATMENT ASSISANT, HUMANA, BAGGIUM - 2014-NOW

Residential cares homes for children with social and psychological issues such as PTSD and other mental issues. With the help of Cognitive Behavior Therapy and Rolemodel methodology, we making sure that the children learn how to be self-propelled.

PARENT RELIEVER, SDN MAJORNA/LINNÉ - 2014

Parent reliever takes care of the parents children for a period of time, so they can do other household duties. Often are the children disabled, both physical or mentally.

BARTENDER, JAZZHUSET - 2010-2013

Making drinks and getting people tipsy. Swedens most popular Indie club.

DEBT COLLECTOR, ALEKTUM INKASSO - 2009-2010

Arrange and purpose amortization plans for people who got their bills in collection agency. Documentation and monitoring was a part of the job to make sure that the debtor paid the bills.

EDUCATION

FORSBERGS SCHOOL, STOCKHOLM - COPYWRITER 2016-2018

OTHER MERITS

 $\operatorname{\mathsf{Did}}$ an internship at NORD DDB, as a Copywriter.

Pro bono-freelancing for PR-Agency A World Beneath.

Speak fluently swedish and farsi, English with a weird swedish accent and german.

REFERENCES

References are given out by request.